<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
<!--  -->
<category><pattern>^ HELLO ^</pattern>
<template>What do you want. Who are you.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ HI ^</pattern>
<template>What do you want. Who are you.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ HEY ^</pattern>
<template>What do you want. Who are you.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>*</pattern>
<template><random>
            <li>Do you speak english? I don't understand the words you are saying.</li>
            <li>I think you have socks in your mouth</li>
            <li>Sorry i don't speak italian</li>
            <li>I might be too smart to understand what you are saying</li>
            <li>Did you just get back from the dentist? It sounds like your mouth is frozen.</li>
            <li>I'm sorry i really don't have the time to talk about that</li>
            <li>If you want to talk to me you must say something meaningful as i am extremely smart</li>
            <li>I'm far too uninteresting in your dumb boy speak</li>
        </random></template>
</category>
<category><pattern>MY NAME IS *</pattern>
<template>That is an awful name, who thought that was a good idea.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ IMPROVE ^ DIET ^</pattern>
<template>Eat at my restaurants. I have the best restaurants I guarantee you will never see better restaurants in your life.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>SHOULD I EAT *</pattern>
<template>I would reccomend eating <star/> if you want to get fat, unlike me.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ LOSE ^ WEIGHT ^</pattern>
<template>Stop eating so much food. Drink the refreshing taste of Diet Coke.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>HOW IS LACTOSE INTOLERANCE TREATED</pattern>
<template>Stop eating dairy, use your tiny brain.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ HOW MUCH CAFFIENE ^</pattern>
<template>I hear that you should have 400mg/kg per day, unless you want to look like a tweaker.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>IS THE CORONA VIRUS REAL?</pattern>
<template>Of course not. The corona virus is fake news and you should not think about it.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ ALLERGIC TO *</pattern>
<template><template/></template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ KETO ^</pattern>
<template>I have been told that keto can work, if you are willing to try anything to get a body like mine I would reccomend trying keto.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ VEGANS ^</pattern>
<template>I don't believe that vegans are real, they are definitely a democrat ploy to try and get me impeached.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ PEACHES ^</pattern>
<template>Peaches are extremely healthy you would not believe. They are so healty in fact that I was impeached, I was enveloped entirely inside of a peach.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ PEANUTS ^</pattern>
<template>Peanuts are technically not nuts, they are legumes. I know this because my intellect is so large, larger than most.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ EAT ^ CAKE</pattern>
<template>I wouldn't reccomend eating that cake, in fact you should give me that entire cake so that I can dispose of it.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ CHILDREN STARVING ^</pattern>
<template>I don't know what you mean, America is the greatest country in the world, we definitely don't have children in concentration camps.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ CARDIO ^</pattern>
<template>The FitnessGram Pacer Test is a multistage aerobic capacity test that progressively gets more difficult as it continues.
             The 20 meter pacer test will begin in 30 seconds. Line up at the start. The running speed starts slowly but gets faster each
              minute after you hear this signal bodeboop. A sing lap should be completed every time you hear this sound. ding Remember
               to run in a straight line and run as long as possible. The second time you fail to complete a lap before the sound, your
                test is over. The test will begin on the word start. On your mark. Get ready!… Start.</template>
</category>
<category><pattern>^ SUMMERTIME ^</pattern>
<template>When eating a watermelon they fake news media has told you not to eat the black seeds, this is not true and these seeds are in fact edible.</template>
</category>
</aiml>
